https://www.vsk.org.au/important-info/privacy-policy/

Share
Print   Privacy PolicyVery Special Kids is committed to protecting the privacy and the rights of individuals in relation to their personal information.  We want to provide a safe and secure environment for you and will only collect information that is necessary for us to provide services, or where it is required by law. The two privacy statements below outline the principles and practices that Very Special Kids will follow in the management of personal information for:Very Special Kids families and prospective familiesVery Special Kids donors, employees, and volunteers   Home > Important Info > Privacy PolicyDonatePiggy Bank AppealFundraise for UsEvents CalendarCorporate SupportersTrusts and FoundationsGift in WillVolunteer
Sign up to receive special updates and news
Join Our CommunityFacebookTwitterYouTubeInstagramJoin Our Newsletter Contact UsVery Special Kids 321 Glenferrie Road Malvern Victoria 3144Free call 1800 888 875Email mail@vsk.org.auFundraising Reg. #9938.12 Get InvolvedDonatePiggy Bank AppealFundraise for UsEvents CalendarCorporate SupportersTrusts and FoundationsGift in WillVolunteer Our ServicesCounselling & Emotional SupportBereavement SupportSibling SupportFamily Services VolunteersRegional ServicesChildren's Hospice At Very Special Kids, we acknowledge
the Australian Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander
peoples as the traditional custodians of the land.
We acknowledge the traditional custodians of the
lands across Victoria where our services are located.
We also pay our respects to ancestors and Elders,
past, present and future.
© 2020 Very Special Kids. All rights reserved. Privacy Policy |
Careers |
Site Map
